24, that indication of Pastor First Christmas Mr. Bradn Butler? Please pardon me I'm probably God we love you got it weird so grateful
That some many good people in leadership here on our city and the last week were prayed for unity
And peace You gave us this to where great full from what
We've done force
And we pray that you would continue to give us those things as well
the digital, whatever it is.
Four vote in buttons got to personal purchase
five budget amendment number 24-10
receiving spending donations
collected today for
Christmas decorations
decoration as donation
21007 dollars
and moving
amounts needed 3580
$90
to complete the 57,46 dollar purchase
at downtown Monocrist-Miston who continued
collecting donations
and to repay their machine pay fund
for $35,893.
So I put an amended amendment
that you're desk on those described in our air
so a amount
should be expensed out as
The 57460
For total amount of
decorations
And from what i understand
there is
a discount that goes away
on March 31st
which is why this amendment
I just give you
were moving some funds
from actually the GNA budget
The City Manager's Budget
to there
with an expectation of
donations
still come in and we'll replace
That.
Make motion,
We approve based
On Corrected Number
I'll sign it
Is sent up
No vote
Hi
Williams
hi
Parker
Alright
Thank You
Six
Got your list
I'm sure
I should have approved
Sorry
Hey
Hi
Don't pull
Hi.
Okay, sorry?
Seven minutes from the Mark 4th of 2024 with a read.
All right
Take it
You step on the way
Alright
Hey good L Straton Edmund and Palmer Claim for your licensing amount
1,395 dollars
So may I remember some counsel you have an Indonesian packet
For what else strattin'
This is four dispersed per January 22nd
24th of February 16, 2024
On behalf the city and my I'm a focused on reviewing
Pleading's filings in other documentation
Up to an including
Dam safety issues
The relaxing state plan
Contaminated sediment transport study
In-half amendment
And circuit court of appeals follow up
Of 750000 budget
For GREA claims
499,525 dollars of it
If current invoice totally 1,395
Proved and leave you a balance
Of $498.130
And 55 cents for this fiscal year
Most two per second
Hi
Now in touch tech client
For the OSHO River
2D modeling
For the first time in the year
So you have an invoice for current services
From November 25th
2023 through December 31st
2023 of behalf
This is where The OSHO River 2D modeling
Which was primary engineering effort
During this period
As well as communications between
The city, flooding and relaxing
The main event threatened
Of the 750000 budget
For GREA claims
Current balance is now 498,335
Give in
If you approve this
10656 dollar
Invoice that will give
Meaning balanced
This fiscal year
The second question
This 2D modeling we keep talking about it
Is there going to be data available at some point?
Absolutely
We could give a dive
To present
We have modelling that
That the legal teams
They presented in
Some of their reports
But if you are wanted
If you have a discussion
If it had to do with strategy
Around how this is being used
To the presentation of
The data
Do a presentation
I would like
You know what
What's reality and
We've been told
Absolutely
What we are paying for is this work
And I know they present a lot of
They use it
For Davis Wright to make
In their filings
But the information
Is something
We want
To be great
I think
I would like to
Yeah
I think it would be excellent for us to all the educated on that
So they are never about things
We can speak
Intelligently when we approach by not just our citizens but other
Interested parties who may
Will
Interested in cutting into our sort of town
Start businesses
Completely agree
To make new to them
They're based on that
To the board
Accurate fire equipment
And a contract to serve as fired
I think it's our sprinkler system of goods
A pretty contracted upon
The submission
Of all required contract documents and authorized
It should be a trust manager or has that need
To sign
Those to proceed
Service includes testing, maintaining
If needed preparing or placing.
The first thing
To be a firm and accurate fire equipment
Accurate is help us on some things in the past
And also my mobile protection
First to companies
My mobile fire
In APS did not quote
An accurate Fire Equipment came
It cost 50
To do fire extinguishers
One-on-one
Two sprinkler systems
We felt that going with one company
To stay on top of everything
Might be a more efficient way
to not get things out
A day and have the question approval
We're under we've passed
Dollar figures
To compare these numbers
What will pay for dollar hour
For example, per hours
It was a little bit lower
That's fair
And I agree with your statement
One company deal
Is the best way to do it
Because they're keeping documentation
It is right thing
To compare what we were doing before
If you are going
Well, this was by hour
They did fire extinguishers
They will give us two options
And we'll choose whichever one is going to be better
Under the circumstances
As far as it has been, those are just once here in The Kitchen
It's down
Oh
All of them coming
Yes
Okay
Perfect
Second
Hi
Renew contract agreement
To report service
Stella viral in all services
And B3 construction
Of tipping fees and transportation fees
For solid waste disposal
Continue to upon the submission of all required contract documents
On these
They're just coming up
Time
And I'm still an environmental last year
Gave us a break of $1.95 less than WCA
That was actually using them for this
They're not going to change any pricing moving forward
We recommend renewing that contract
B3 construction is the one
The takes are demolition material
Or they don't take in
The purchase homes and buildings that we have to demolish
And they're going keep the contract at same pricing
So, will be recommend
Going with that
In then Republic services
Last year's WCA
It was gonna be 41.51 per ton
They tried
To give us aggressive as it could
Which is continually going up
And it hits around 7.23 per cent on the last three year trend
They tried to come in at a 6 and 1 half
We got them down
To 5% increase
Under this probably would not be
A good situation put out to bed again over
Just because of
The big gap that we had
Last time in the competitor that we would be going after
Would BWCA
Which was almost done for price
So, I recommend sticking with Republic and taking a 5% increase
That's CPI
They look at annual
They will come down
It looks like they looked
The last three years
And annually is what
It's been average in 7.23 per cent
Probably the fact that there was such a huge gap
And we don't have very many people to go out and pull into beds
That is more why I am waiting
To say, We need it
This
Tonner where were you going
They are inside
Still think thats gonna be
The cheapest way of doing this
I am going to try and find out
The most stupid
Second
Hi
Thank you
Discussion policy
And 116
Approval
An authorized trust manager
To sign the contract
So, council you have in front of
You a contract
From
A buyer to purchase three properties
On Main Street the 3 addresses that are listed
Originally
The city had purchased these properties
Specifically
To see if there was some type
Of event venue or something we might want
As other things continue
We have a buyer who has made us
Very, very good offer
For all three properties to be developed
At this time I mean that is really what i think the discussion for
The council
Is of interest
To let go
This property at
The way that i think he is committed to the city
This a somebody who thinks it will be doing
A lot of different things around town
As far as investment
He has been vetted
As an incredible buyer and developer
And I
Think its very credible offer you have heard
It would allow us not only
To pay back
But we would also allow you some other funds that
I think the mayor could expand upon a little further
We will put
That is in contract
And thats where our new police department detects his offices
It's for their currently located
This agreement
Will it allowed them to stay there until such time
Again, till this property
Is needed
To be developed
So we are talking about the road
Still yet
And he is agreed to release
The property back
That was a good order
A dollar amount
It's 90 days notice
This would allow us
To continue
Utilize that facility
Which previously was known as pay centers
As well i have made attraction
Which is an empty building we have used
In several different events
Different capacities
We use it most recently
During the Christmas toy drive
To allow us to store their toys
Future council
I don't know
You are not going
So from 3 inches which its currently defined
12 inch
You could provide a contingent of the money
Are we in close to our new armary
Reserved building?
The fans are still saying they're looking at 2025
We closed for 25
To your way
That's $12
It is not about gear welcome
So the legal description on one of you is not correct
We are going to prove this
The contingency that Ben already has it right there
I am a corrected legal
Distriction with
It could be more
To further specify
And we talked about here as main attraction
Previous main attractions
That was what business last business
$391,171
To go to the MSU repay
For money they loaned
Make the purchase of properties
100 thousand
For a main street program
And 58k
To invest in the business decoration
Second
Third